export const PROBLEM_OF_MONTH_2010 = [
    {
        month: "January",
        year: 2010,
        question: "1001q.pdf",
        solution: "1001a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Neacsu Adrian", affiliation: "Fırat University" },
            { name: "Ayse Bülbül", affiliation: "METU" },
            { name: "Seda Yıldırım", affiliation: "METU" },
            { name: "Müge Kasacı", affiliation: "METU" },
            { name: "Mahmut Sait Okyay", affiliation: "Bursa Ozel Nilüfer Piri Reis Lisesi" }
        ]
    },
    {
        month: "February",
        year: 2010,
        question: "1002q.pdf",
        solution: "1002a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Irena Tasevska", affiliation: "Bilkent University" },
            { name: "Kerem Gönen", affiliation: "Bilkent University" },
            { name: "Seval Aydın", affiliation: "Bilkent University" }
        ]
    },
    {
        month: "March",
        year: 2010,
        question: "1003q.pdf",
        solution: "1003a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Müge Kasacı", affiliation: "METU" },
            { name: "Seda Yıldırım", affiliation: "METU" },
            { name: "Kerem Gönen", affiliation: "Bilkent University" },
            { name: "Seval Aydın", affiliation: "Bilkent University" }
        ]
    },
    {
        month: "April",
        year: 2010,
        question: "1004q.pdf",
        solution: "1004a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Kerem Gönen", affiliation: "Bilkent University" },
            { name: "Seval Aydın", affiliation: "Bilkent University" },
            { name: "Seda Yıldırım", affiliation: "METU" },
            { name: "Müge Kasacı", affiliation: "METU" }
        ]
    },
    {
        month: "May",
        year: 2010,
        question: "1005q.pdf",
        solution: "1005a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Kerem Gönen", affiliation: "Bilkent University" },
            { name: "Seval Aydın", affiliation: "Bilkent University" }
        ]
    },
    {
        month: "June",
        year: 2010,
        question: "1006q.pdf",
        solution: "1006a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Kerem Gönen", affiliation: "Bilkent University" },
            { name: "Seval Aydın", affiliation: "Bilkent University" }
        ]
    },
    {
        month: "July",
        year: 2010,
        question: "1007q.pdf",
        solution: "1007a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Kerem Gönen", affiliation: "Bilkent University" },
            { name: "Seval Aydın", affiliation: "Bilkent University" }
        ]
    },
    {
        month: "September",
        year: 2010,
        question: "1009q.pdf",
        solution: "1009a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Kerem Gönen", affiliation: "Bilkent University" },
            { name: "Seval Aydın", affiliation: "Bilkent University" }
        ]
    },
    {
        month: "October",
        year: 2010,
        question: "1010q.pdf",
        solution: "1010a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Kerem Gönen", affiliation: "Bilkent University" },
            { name: "Seval Aydın", affiliation: "Bilkent University" }
        ]
    },
    {
        month: "November",
        year: 2010,
        question: "1011q.pdf",
        solution: "1011a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Kerem Gönen", affiliation: "Bilkent University" },
            { name: "Seval Aydın", affiliation: "Bilkent University" }
        ]
    },
    {
        month: "December",
        year: 2010,
        question: "1012q.pdf",
        solution: "1012a.pdf",
        solvers: [
            { name: "Kerem Gönen", affiliation: "Bilkent University" },
            { name: "Seval Aydın", affiliation: "Bilkent University" }
        ]
    }
];
